Akshat Aggarwal

9891029069 akshat.aggarwal9812@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/akshat-aggarwal-27380/

Profile

Motivated and personable student pursuing B.tech in Computer Science with specialisation in Artificial Intelligence at the prestigious Netaji Subhas University of Technology (CGPA - 8.9). I have a strong theoretical background in programming and problem solving.

Work History

GOOGLE CLOUD MENTORSHIP - SEP 2021 - OCT 2022

- Participated in activities to handle cloud data and performed actions on the data to make it more useful and secure.
- Learned how to manage a virtual machine which is essential to work with client and employees as it provides much needed flexibility.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.
- Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule.

GRAPHICS TEAM, PRAYAS SOCIETY - SEP 2021 - DEC 2021

- Leaned how to create a basic level of Graphic Designing to create beautiful poster and posts.
- Worked in team to learn team building and coordination.

Education

Maharaja Agrasen Model School - New Delhi High School Diploma, 2019

Netaji Subhas University of Technology - New Delhi

Bachelor's of Technology: Computer Science And Engineering, 2020-2024

Skills

C++	***
HTML, CSS, Javascript	♦♦♦
Mongo DB	♦•
Express JS	♦•
Node JS	♦♦♦
React	♦♦♦

Projects

https://github.com/akshat6745/text-Flow-Mern

(Deployed Link -> $\underline{\text{https://merntextflow.herokuapp.com/}}$)

https://github.com/akshat6745/DSC-Profile